{"data":[{"question":"And the beauty is that there are so little people to share all this money.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"beauty","b":"that","c":"little","d":"this","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Little-> few","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1980 the Sultan met an air hostess calling Mariam Bell and fell in love with her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"met","b":"calling","c":"fell","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Calling->called","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Factory chimneys give out smoke that containing sulphur dioxide and nitrogen oxide.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Factory","b":"give","c":"containing","d":"and","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Containing-> contains","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"When it rains, these acids dissolve in the rain and make it to be acidic.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"it","b":"dissolve","c":"in","d":"to be","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To be-> be","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Acid rain is believed be the worst pollution problem of all.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"be","c":"worst","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Be-> to be","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Acid rain has harmed aquatic life by to turn many lakes into lifeless bodies of water.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has harmed","b":"to turn","c":"into","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To turn-> turning","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"It is not possible to do this on a large enough scale to save all the lake.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"possible","c":"large","d":"lake","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Lake-> lakes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Car exhaust fumes contain carbon monoxide and lead which are high poisonous.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"exhaust","b":"contain","c":"which","d":"high","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- High-> highly","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"1.6 billion gallons were sold every year, in over one hundred and sixty countries.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"in","c":"hundred","d":"countries","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Were-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"It is certainly that Coca-Cola will be drunk far into the twenty-first century.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"certainly","b":"drunk","c":"into","d":"twenty-first","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Certainly-> certain","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}